babeshows.co.uk 2018-07-24

# UK Babe Channels Forum

**_  
UK Babe Channels Forum Privacy Policy_**

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our forum members and this policy sets out how we store and use your personal information.

The forum uses cookies. By using the forum and agreeing to this policy you expressly agree to the use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

**(A)       Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

The forum uses two types of cookies, session cookies and persistent cookies. It uses persistent cookies to identify you when you visit and it uses session cookies to open and close a session (i.e. to allow login to and logout of the site). Persistent cookies are stored on your computer until deleted, but session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser.

Most browsers allow you to deny/disable cookies very easily, but blocking all cookies in this way will make it impossible for you to login to the forum.

**(B)       Collection of personal information**

We collect and store the following kinds of personal information:

(1) the email address that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters.

(2) information about your visits to and use of the forum, such as your IP address including therefore your internet service provider and your geographical location, your browser type and version, your computer operating system, your referral source, the length of your visit, your page views and your forum navigation.

(3) any other information that you choose to send to us. 

Information that we collect is stored and processed in the USA which is the country in which the forum is located. You expressly agree to this.

You can access the email address we hold for you in your User CP (control panel) and amend it at any time.

**(C)       Use of personal information**

We may use your personal information to:

(1) improve your browsing experience by personalising the forum.

(2) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested.

(3) administer the forum, i.e. send you emails from the forum admin.

(4) send you marketing communications relating to the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you. You can opt out of this in your User CP (control panel).

(5) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you regarding the forum.

If you post personal information in the forum it is at your own risk (as we are obviously unable to prevent the use or misuse of such information by others once you have published it on the worldwide web). However, please note that personal information posted in the forum is often removed by the forum staff. In particular any email addresses and telephone numbers which are posted in the forum are likely to be quickly removed by the forum moderators.

We will not under any circumstances provide your email address to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing or for any other commercial purpose.

**(D)       Security**

We will take all reasonable technical and organisational measures to prevent the disclosure of your registration email address and any other email address that you subsequently use. Your stored email address cannot be accessed by the forum moderators and is therefore not generally available to them.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. Forum staff will not ask you for your password and the site only requires it to be used when you login. You can change your password at any time in your User CP (control panel).

Please note that if your forum account is hacked the hacker will have access to your stored email address. The importance of account security cannot be over-emphasised, as the hacker will also be able to impersonate you in the forum. Again, you can change your password at any time in your User CP (control panel).

The forum contains many links to other websites. We have no control over such third party websites and we are not responsible for their privacy policies or their practices.

**(E)      Disclosure**

We may disclose information about you to members of the forum staff if it is regarded as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy policy.

In addition we may disclose your personal information to the extent that we are required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings or to provide the information to anyone who we believe may successfully apply to a court for the disclosure of the information.

**(F)       Contact**

If you have any questions concerning the forum’s privacy policy or the handling of your personal information please email us at [admin@babechannels.co.uk](mailto:admin@babechannels.co.uk)

We may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on the site.  You may want to check this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any changes which may have been made.

We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by PM (personal message) in the forum. If you wish, you can opt out of this service in your User CP (control panel).
